So, this is Sosuke.
那么   这就是宗介
How do you do?
你好吗
Are you Ponyo's mother?
你是波妞的妈妈吗
Yes. You brought my daughter safely here. Thank you.
是的   你把我女儿安全送到这里   谢谢你
Sosuke, Ponyo opened a magic well because she wants very much to be human.
宗介   波妞打开了一口魔法井  因为她非常想成为人
To become a real girl, she need you to accept and love her as she truly is.
要变成一个真正的女孩   她需要你接受和爱她本来的样子
You know that Ponyo was a fish, don't you?
你知道波妞以前是一条鱼   不是吗
Mhmm
嗯哼
And you know her as a human.Your drop of blood did that.
而且你知道她是一个人  你的一滴血让她变成了人
Oh, that's it. I cut my thumb, then Ponyo licked it and made it better.
哦   原来是这样   我切到了我的拇指   然后波妞舔了一下   它就好多了
So that's how she changed into a human.
原来她是这样变成人的
Could you love her if she moved between two worlds?
她在两个世界来回的话   你能爱她吗
Mhmm. I love all the ponyos.
嗯哼   只要是波妞我都爱
It's a big responsibility but I really love her.
这是一份巨大的责任   但我真的很爱她